

## **Personal Profile**

I am 22 year old .I am an undergraduate student of Computer Science and Engineering at DIU. Now I read in 8th semester (L4TI). At present my CGPA is 3.80. I am a hard worker, honest and responsible person. My hobby is drawing and learning new things.I have been successfully completed Photoshop, Illustrator, Canva, and others are below: MS Word, MS Excel, MS PowerPoint, Make the web page.

# **Education Background**

- Daffodil International University 2022 -Present
  - Attached with club activities
  - -Class representative
- Manikgonj Govt. Mohila Collage 2017-2019
- S.K Govt. Girls High School, Manikgonj
  - Girl Guides

## **Skill and Interest**

•	Graphic Design	88%
•	Microsoft Powerpoint	0078
	N. diamaga of the superal	93%
_	Microsoft word	86%
•	Microsoft excel/google	0070
		71%
•	UI/UX Design	
		51%

# Adiba zaman chowdhury

Undergraduate student

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Office Secretary

Daffodil Prothom Alo Bondhusaval December 2020 - present

- Facilitating communications within an office and fielding interactions with the public.
- Graphics Design Leader

#### **Exicutive Officer**

Iskool 71 | July 2021 - present

• Graphics Design

## Assistant General secretary (Research)

Girls' Computer Programming Club-DIU | July 2022 - present

- · organizing work schedules
- Graphics design

## **Achievement**

- Drawing contest participation.2nd place in whole Bangladesh.
- Programming contest participation
- winner in logo contest many times in freelancer.com
- Graphic Design contest participation

# Language

- Bangla
- English
- Hindi

## **Reach Me At**

- No −524 ,Road No −4
- west Bandutia, Manikgonj 01818995505
- adiba15-3924@diu.edu.bd